so let's see if we understood inclusion
let's say that we have a level 1 and
level 2 cache
that maintain inclusion property let's
say that a dirty block is replaced from
the level 1 cache by something else
and we need to write it back
this right back axis can it be a level 2
hit
and can it be a level 2 miss
so check here
if the right back axis
from level 1 can be a hit in l2
check here
if the right back axis from l1 can be a
level two miss
now let's look at the level one and
level two cache but this time
they make no attempt
to maintain inclusion
again if we have a dirty block replaced
from the level one cache
the level one cache has to write it back
and this right back can it be a level
two hit
and can it be a level two miss